=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 14=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 14 =
ENI Dessert?
حلوى ENI؟
(Invitation to Study Tour Introduction to ENI Dessert)
(دعوة لجولة دراسية مقدمة عن حلوى ENI)
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Mu Li
مو لي
asked me to be your secretary.
طلبت مني أن أكون سكرتيرتك.
You really
أنت حقا
don't remember me at all?
لا تتذكرني إطلاقا؟
Yes, I do.
نعم أفعل.
You are Li's best friend.
أنت أفضل صديق لي.
Since you want to be my secretary,
بما أنك تريد أن تكون سكرتيرتي ،
you can help me
يمكنك مساعدتي
make a list of Li's preferences.
قم بعمل قائمة بتفضيلات Li.
You'll help me, right?
سوف تساعدني ، أليس كذلك؟
In your dreams!
في احلامك!
Blind and heartless.
أعمى وبلا قلب.
I'm pissed off!
أنا غضبان!
No,
رقم،
I need to try again.
أنا بحاجة إلى المحاولة مرة أخرى.
(Li's Preferences; Written by: Tang Xue)
(تفضيلات Li ؛ بقلم: Tang Xue)
Wait!
انتظر!
This is
هذا هو
the list of Li's preferences
قائمة تفضيلات Li
that I made for you.
الذي صنعته لك.
If you can't get her,
إذا لم تستطع الحصول عليها ،
you are a fool!
أنت أبله!
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
She doesn't like me.
هي لا تحبني.
If she doesn't like you,
إذا كانت لا تحبك ،
why does she have your photo
لماذا لديها صورتك
in the office?
في المكتب؟
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Come on!
هيا!
OK!
نعم!
(Li's Preferences; Written by: Tang Xue)
(تفضيلات Li ؛ بقلم: Tang Xue)
(1. Haunted Houses; 2. Ice cream; 3. Baseball)
(1. منازل مسكونة ؛ 2. آيس كريم ؛ 3. بيسبول)
(4. Seafood congee, steak, spaghetti bolognese, mango pizza)
(4.كونجي المأكولات البحرية ، شريحة لحم ، إسباجيتي بولونيز ، بيتزا مانجو)
(Tomorrow is the weekend.)
(غدًا عطلة نهاية الأسبوع).
(Do you want to go to an escape room?)
(هل تريد الذهاب إلى غرفة الهروب؟)
(Mo Chen: Tomorrow is the weekend. Do you want to go to an escape room?)
(Mo Chen: غدًا عطلة نهاية الأسبوع. هل تريد الذهاب إلى غرفة الهروب؟)
(Yes.)
(نعم.)
(Mu Liu: Yes.)
(مو ليو: نعم.)
(1. Haunted Houses; 2. Ice cream)
(1. منازل مسكونة ؛ 2. آيس كريم)
(Yucai Middle School)
(مدرسة Yucai المتوسطة)
Are you afraid?
هل انت خائف؟
So nervous.
متوتر جدا.
I'm afraid?
أنا خائف؟
Don't be scared and cry later.
لا تخف وتبكي لاحقًا.
It's hard to tell who will cry.
من الصعب معرفة من سيبكي.
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا.
I'm not afraid.
أنا لست خائفا.
You're scared.
أنت خائف.
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
do you think
هل تعتقد
there is someone behind us?
هناك شخص ما وراءنا؟
I didn't know you were afraid of ghosts.
لم أكن أعلم أنك خائف من الأشباح.
You're so timid.
أنت خجول جدا.
When was I ever afraid of ghosts?
متى خفت من الأشباح؟
You scared me, OK?
لقد أخفتني ، حسناً؟
You saw what you were like just now.
لقد رأيت ما كنت عليه الآن.
You were trembling.
كنت ترتجف.
Hey,
يا،
be honest with me.
كن صادقا معي.
You have never been to Haunted Houses, right?
أنت لم تذهب من قبل إلى المنازل المسكونة ، أليس كذلك؟
I...
أنا...
I'm usually so busy.
أنا عادة مشغول جدا.
How can I go to Haunted Houses?
كيف يمكنني الذهاب إلى المنازل المسكونة؟
OK, I believe you.
حسنا انا اصدقك.
Hey.
يا.
What?
ماذا؟
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪
♪The resin lights the torch♪
♪ الراتنج يضيء الشعلة ♪
♪To brighten the starry sky at night♪
لتفتيح السماء المرصعة بالنجوم ليلاً ♪
♪Lightning splits the sky♪
البرق يقسم السماء
♪The earth is silent♪
الأرض صامتة ♪
♪You and me♪
♪ أنت وأنا ♪
I took the wrong one.
أخذت الخطأ.
Oh, it's OK.
أوه ، لا بأس.
Anyway, we...
على أي حال ، نحن ...
♪Half an ocean with a moon♪
♪ نصف محيط مع قمر
Mu Liu,
مو ليو ،
actually, I...
في الواقع ، أنا ...
I'm actually happy today.
أنا سعيد فعلاً اليوم.
Then,
ثم،
I can seriously
يمكنني بجدية
deal with the Mu's affairs.
التعامل مع شؤون مو.
♪Heart broken love♪
♪ قلب مكسور الحب ♪
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
(What took you so long to answer the phone?)
(ما الذي استغرق منك وقتًا طويلاً للرد على الهاتف؟)
(Mu Bingyun failed.)
(فشل Mu Bingyun.)
I expected it.
كنت أتوقع ذلك.
(The top priority now)
(الأولوية القصوى الآن)
(is to stop Mu Liu from taking power.)
(هو منع Mu Liu من تولي السلطة.)
I'll give you a trump card.
سأعطيك ورقة رابحة.
This is the last time I can help you.
هذه آخر مرة يمكنني مساعدتك فيها.
Don't forget the accident.
لا تنسى الحادث.
(You're helping yourself!)
(أنت تساعد نفسك!)
(You...)
(أنت...)
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪